joy in place of sorrow.
He who from you became incarnate,
God and man has directed to life
him who fell from it.
Hallelujah, hallelujah,
glory to you, O God.
hallelujah, glory to you, O God.
Hallelujah, hallelujah,
Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
Vox as ioth eos
Again and again in peace
Let us pray to the Lord
Lord have mercy
Help us, save us, have mercy on us
And protect us, O God, by your grace
Lord, have mercy.
Remembering our all-holy, immaculate, most blessed
and glorious Lady the Theotokos
and ever-Virgin Mary,
with all the saints, let us commend ourselves
and one another
and our whole life to Christ our God.
For blessed is your name and glorified is your kingdom.
Death has been put to death,
and we have been brought back to life.
Therefore we extol him and cry out,
O Christ our God,
you are blessed,
for so was your good place.
Pleasure, glory to you.
Anahmes.
The Lord is the Son of God.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Πατ'ρ Παγκοκράτορ, Κύριε Ιερονογένες, Ιησού Χριστέ και Αγία Νέα.
Κύριε ο Θεός, ο Αγλός του Θεού, ο Υιός του Πατρός,
ο αίραν την αγαπία του κόσμου
πελέησον ημίδη
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Θεού πατρόσον η.
Κάθε κάστην ημέρα ανευραγίσωσε
και εν μέσω τ' όνομά σου
εις τον αιώνας
και εις τον αιώνα του αιώνος.
Καταξιώσον, Κύριε,
τ' ημέρα θα αυτήν
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Υπάρθη τους φυλακτήνε ημάς.
Ευλογητός η Κύριε ο Θεός των Παθέρω αν ημών,
και εν ετών και δε δοσσμένων
το όγδομά σου εις τους αιώνας αμήν.
Γέννη το κύριε, το έντεο σου εφίβας,
καθαπεριλθύσαμεν επίσθε.
Ευλογητώσυ Κύριε,
διδαξόμεν τα δικαιώματά σου.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Τα δικαιώματά σου. Ευλογητώσ' ειμί, Κύριε, διδαξόν με τα δικαιώματά σου.
Κύριε, καταφύγει, εγενήθησ' ειμί, εν γενεά και εν γενεά.
Εγώ είπα, Κύριε, ελεήσω με
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Άγιος αθάνατος ελέης όνει μας.
Άγιος ο Θεός, Άγιος ισχύρος,
Δόξα πατρί και Υιό και Άγιον πνεύματι,
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Μάτσος.
Σήμερον σωτηρία το κόσμο γεγόνε,
άσομεν το Αναστάθι εκτάμου,
και αρκικό της ζωής ημών.
Τα θεών γαρτών θανάτων,
Στον φάνατος
Blessed is the kingdom of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit,
now and forever
and to the end.
ages of ages.
Amen.
In peace let us pray to the
Lord.
Lord have mercy.
For the peace of
God and for the salvation
of our souls let us pray
to the Lord.
Lord have
mercy.
for peace in the
For the whole world, for the stability of the holy churches of God, and for the unity of all, let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For this holy house and for those who enter it with faith, reverence, and the fear of God, let us pray to the Lord.
for our
Father and Archbishop Nicholas, the Honorable Presbyters, the Deacons in the service of Christ,
and all the clergy and people, let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For our country, the President, and all those in public service, let us pray to the Lord.
For this parish and city, for every city and country, and for the faithful who live in them, let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For favorable weather and abundance of the fruits of the earth, and for peaceful times, let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, amen.
Have mercy.
For travelers by land, sea and air,
for the sick, the suffering,
the captives, and for their salvation,
let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For our deliverance from all affliction,
wrath, danger, and distress,
let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, I am.
Help us, save us, have mercy on us, and protect us, O God, by your grace.
Lord, have mercy.
Remembering our most holy, pure, blessed, and glorious Lady the Theotokos,
and ever-Virgin Mary with all the same.
Let us commit ourselves and one another
and our whole life to Christ our God.
To you, O Lord.
For to you belong all glory, honor, and worship
to the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit
now and forever and to the ages of ages.
on the cross, Jesus' death on the cross, that he was able to destroy death for us.
And through his death, resurrection, and promises resurrection to all of us.
The Holy Cross sits on the altar every day throughout the year. And there are just three
occasions during the church year that it is brought out in the midst of the people,
so that they may take courage and strength, that they may continue.
the rigors of the fast. Then last Sunday we commemorated St. John of the Ladder,
who wrote this beautiful work, The Ladder of Divine Ascent, of which Father Michael spoke
so beautifully last Sunday. He likened St. John of the Ladder, likened this journey through life
as really like climbing a ladder,
and every rung on the ladder is a...
a vice that needs to be overcome,
and a virtue to be attained.
30 rungs.
And once we get to the top,
we'll experience what the church knows as theoses.
That is, vision of God.
Vision of God.
As Jesus said in the Beatitudes,
blessed are the pure in heart,
for they shall see.
with the fear of God, with faith, and with love drawn near.
Ong de Paraná,
Thank you.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE